Armageddon
Amageddon
Shoot
Imma get 'em
Imma get em
Imma get ’em
Imma get 'em
Imma get'em
Shoot
Watch Uh
Imma bite back Uh
When the thick darkness
Saat kegelapan pekat
深い暗闇が
짙은 어둠이
เมื่อความมืดมิด
浓重的黑暗
當深深的黑暗
Khi màn đêm đen tối
Stops ya, Uh
menghalangiku Uh
立ちはだかる時には Uh
막아설 땐 Uh
ขวางกั้นเธอ Uh
阻挡时 Uh
阻擋之時 Uh
Chặn phía trước mặt Uh
One step forward
Selangkah ke depan
一歩前へ
한 걸음 앞으로
ก้าวไปข้างหน้าหนึ่งก้าว
往前一步
往前跨出一步
Tiến một bước
Swoop, It's bad
Terbang It’s bad
舞い込んだ It’s bad
날아든 It’s bad
ถลาเข้ามา It's bad
飞来的 It's bad
飛來的 It's bad
Bay tới It's bad
Gone, Feedback
Feedback yang hilang
消えた Feedback
사라진 Feedback
Feedback หายไป
消失的 Feedback
Biến mất Feedback
Hit it, Code black Uh
Code black yang dimulai Uh
始まった Code black Uh
시작된 Code black Uh
เริ่มแล้ว Code black Uh
开始的 Code black Uh
開始的 Code black Uh
Bắt đầu Code black Uh
Getting deeper
Semakin larut dalam
更けていく
깊어가
ลึกลงไป
越来越深
越來越深
Sâu dần
This chaotic night
malam yang kacau
入り乱れる夜
혼란스러운 밤
คืนที่วุ่นวาย
混乱的夜
混亂的夜
Màn đêm hỗn loạn
And sticky thick nightmare creeps
Mimpi buruk kembali merasuk lebih dalam
悪夢はまた色濃く滲んでいく
악몽은 또 짙게 번져가
ฝันร้ายกำลังแพร่กระจายลึกลงไปอีกครั้ง
噩梦又再度深刻蔓延
惡夢又再度深刻蔓延
Ác mộng dần lan ra
Tryna hide something
Berusaha menyembunyikan sesuatu
何かを隠そうとしている
뭔갈 숨기려고 해
พยายามซ่อนบางสิ่งบางอย่าง
试图隐藏什么
試圖隱藏什麼
Định giấu đi một cái gì đó
I got it, I got it
Riding in on the chaos, then
Melalui kekacauan
カオスに紛れて
혼돈을 타고
อยู่ท่ามกลางความวุ่นวาย
裹挟着混沌
乘著混沌
Lợi dụng lúc hỗn loạn
Strike, Killing like
Menyerang Killing like
襲いかかる Killing like
덮쳐 Killing like
โจมตี Killing like
袭来 Killing like
突襲 Killing like
Ập tới Killing like
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
Cause I wanna see
’Cause I wanna see
I wanna see truly
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
Come to me, closer, closer
Datanglah padaku. Datanglah
私に近づいてきて 近づいてきて
내게 다가와 다가와
เข้ามาใกล้ๆฉันสิ เข้ามาอีกนิด
向我靠近 靠近
往我靠近 再靠近
Hãy tiến lại gần em tiến lại gần
Imma get it
Done
(Aw wayo wayo)
Aimed at ya, Get it, gone
Membidik ke arah mu Get it, gone
君に向かって狙いを定める Get it, gone
널 향해 겨눠 Get it, gone
เล็งเป้าไปที่เธอ Get it, gone
瞄准你 Get it, gone
瞄準你 Get it, gone
Hướng tới anh Get it, gone
(Aw wayo wayo)
Now I finish ya, Better run
Sekarang aku akan menghabisimu
もう君を仕留める Better run
이젠 널 끝내 Better run
ตอนนี้สำหรับเธอมันจบแล้ว Better run
现在了结你 Better run
準備將你了結 Better run
Bây giờ anh sẽ kết thúc Better run
(You and I we know no end, You gonna, gonna)
(kau dan aku yang tak tahu akhir ini You gonna, gonna)
(終わりを知らない君と私 You gonna, gonna)
(끝을 모르는 너와 나 You gonna, gonna)
(เธอและฉันที่ยังไม่รู้ตอนจบ You gonna, gonna)
(不知道结局的你和我 You gonna, gonna）
(不知道結局的你與我 You gonna, gonna)
(Chúng ta không bao giờ có cái kết You gonna, gonna)
Smash it no doubt, Done
Hancurkan tanpa ragu-ragu Done
ぶち壊す 躊躇せずに Done
깨트려 거침없이 Done
ทำลายมันโดยไม่ลังเล Done
毫无顾忌地打破 Done
全都大肆破壞掉 Done
Không chần chừ phá vỡ Done
(Go way up, way up)
Full shot pull it up Armageddon
Imma get 'em
Imma get ’em
Imma get' em
Imma get 'em
Shoot
Imma get ’em
Imma get 'em
Imma get' em
Hey ya
Hey Ya
My alter ego
Diriku yang lain
もう一人の私
또 다른 나
ตัวฉันอีกคน
另一个我
另一個我
Là một con người khác
Don't block our flow
Jangan hentikan kami
私たちを止めないで
우릴 막지 마
อย่าขว้างพวกเรา
不要阻挡我们
別阻擋我們
Đừng có ngăn cản chúng ta
We never play nice
Shoot
A perfect Pair
Pair yang sempurna
完璧な Pair
완벽한 Pair
Pair ที่สมบูรณ์แบบ
完美的 Pair
Pair hoàn hảo
You're my identical Soul
Kaulah Soul yang sama
君はそっくりな Soul
넌 똑같은 Soul
เธอคือ Soul เดียวกัน
你是一样的 Soul
你是一樣的 Soul
Anh Soul giống em
Three to get ready
We're Shoot and go
Kita Shoot and go
私たちは Shoot and go
우린 Shoot and go
พวกเรา Shoot and go
我们 Shoot and go
我們 Shoot and go
Chúng ta Shoot and go
Roam unafraid
Jelajahi tanpa rasa takut
何も恐れず駆け巡る
겁 없이 누벼
ไปไหนก็ได้โดยไม่ต้องกลัว
无所畏惧地穿梭
無畏地穿梭
Không sợ hãi mà tiến tới
Leading me is the Way
Way yang membimbingku
私を導く Way
날 이끄는 Way
Way ที่นำพาฉันไป
引领着我的 Way
帶領著我的 Way
Way chỉ dẫn em
Bang chitty Bang
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
Yes I'm gonna see
Yes I’m gonna see
I'm gonna see, want it
I’m gonna see, want it
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
The answer, I hear it, I hear it
Jawabannya mulai terdengar
答えが聞こえてくる 聞こえてくる
답이 들려와 들려와
ฉันได้ยินคำตอบ ได้ยินมัน
听见 听见答案
聽見了 聽見了答案
Câu trả lời vọng lại
Imma get it
Done
(Aw wayo wayo)
Aimed at ya, Get it, gone
Membidik ke arah mu Get it, gone
君に向かって狙いを定める Get it, gone
널 향해 겨눠 Get it, gone
เล็งเป้าไปที่เธอ Get it, gone
瞄准你 Get it, gone
瞄準你 Get it, gone
Hướng tới anh Get it, gone
(Aw wayo wayo)
Now I finish ya, Better run
Sekarang aku akan menghabisimu
もう君を仕留める Better run
이젠 널 끝내 Better run
ตอนนี้สำหรับเธอมันจบแล้ว Better run
现在了结你 Better run
準備將你了結 Better run
Bây giờ anh sẽ kết thúc Better run
(You and I we know no end, You gonna, gonna)
(kau dan aku yang tak tahu akhir ini You gonna, gonna)
(終わりを知らない君と私 You gonna, gonna)
(끝을 모르는 너와 나 You gonna, gonna)
(เธอและฉันที่ยังไม่รู้ตอนจบ You gonna, gonna)
(不知道结局的你和我 You gonna, gonna）
(不知道結局的你與我 You gonna, gonna)
(Chúng ta không bao giờ có cái kết You gonna, gonna)
Smash it no douobt, Done
Hancurkan tanpa ragu-ragu Done
ぶち壊す 躊躇せずに Done
깨트려 거침없이 Done
ทำลายมันโดยไม่ลังเล Done
毫无顾忌地打破 Done
全都大肆破壞掉 Done
Không chần chừ phá vỡ Done
(Go way up, way up)
Full shot pull it up Armageddon
Imma get 'em
Imma get ’em
Imma get' em
Imma get 'em
Drive off the darkness once more
Mengusir kembali kegelapan
また暗闇を追い払って
또 어둠을 몰아내고
ขับไล่ความมืดมิดออกไป
再一次驱散黑暗
將黑暗驅逐
Lại đẩy lùi màn đêm
And so it flowers this Story of us
awal yang membuat bunga mekar story kau dan aku
始まりを咲かせた君と私の Story
시작을 꽃피운 너와 나의 Story
และทำให้ Story ของเราเบ่งบานตั้งแต่เริ่มต้น
开始绽放的 你和我的Story
綻放出開始的你與我的 Story
Story của anh và em bắt đầu nở rộ
You and me, even more flawless
Kita menjadi lebih sempurna
もっと完璧になった私たち
더 완벽해진 우리
เรามีความสมบูรณ์แบบมากขึ้น
变得更加完美的我们
變得更完美的我們
Đôi ta trở nên hoàn hảo hơn
Now define it
Definisikan sekarang
定義する これからは
정의해 이젠
กำหนดมัน ตอนนี้
定义吧 现在
是時候定義了
Hãy làm rõ ý nghĩa
(Armageddon)
My personal definition of Complete
Complete-ku sendiri
私だけの Complete
나만의 Complete
Complete ของฉันเอง
只属于我的 Complete
屬於我的 Complete
Complete của riêng em
I shall lead every part of me
memimpin segalanya
私のすべてを導いていく
내 모든 걸 이끌어
นำทุกสิ่งของฉัน
引领我的一切
帶領我的一切
Chỉ dẫn cho em mọi thứ
Do it all myself
At last complete myself
Mewujudkan diriku yang sempurna
完全な私を作り出す
완전한 나를 이뤄내
ทำให้ฉันสมบูรณ์แบบ
成就完整的我
實現完整的自己
Trở thành một con người hoàn hảo
(Drop)
Throw it back,
throw it back,
throw it back
Born like a queen
Born like a king Ya
Throw it back,
throw it back,
throw it back
Sing it
Panggil
呼んで
불러
เรียกหา
歌唱
Hát lên đi
Imma get 'em
Imma get ’em
Imma get' em
Imma get 'em
Done
(Aw wayo wayo)
Aimed at ya, Get it, gone
Membidik ke arah mu Get it, gone
君に向かって狙いを定める Get it, gone
널 향해 겨눠 Get it, gone
เล็งเป้าไปที่เธอ Get it, gone
瞄准你 Get it, gone
瞄準你 Get it, gone
Hướng tới anh Get it, gone
(Aw wayo wayo)
Now I finish ya, Better run
Sekarang aku akan menghabisimu
もう君を仕留める Better run
이젠 널 끝내 Better run
ตอนนี้สำหรับเธอมันจบแล้ว Better run
现在了结你 Better run
準備將你了結 Better run
Bây giờ anh sẽ kết thúc Better run
(You and I we know no end, You gonna, gonna)
(kau dan aku yang tak tahu akhir ini You gonna, gonna)
(終わりを知らない君と私 You gonna, gonna)
(끝을 모르는 너와 나 You gonna, gonna)
(เธอและฉันที่ยังไม่รู้ตอนจบ You gonna, gonna)
(不知道结局的你和我 You gonna, gonna）
(不知道結局的你與我 You gonna, gonna)
(Chúng ta không bao giờ có cái kết You gonna, gonna)
Smash it no doubt, Done
Hancurkan tanpa ragu-ragu Done
ぶち壊す 躊躇せずに Done
깨트려 거침없이 Done
ทำลายมันโดยไม่ลังเล Done
毫无顾忌地打破 Done
全都大肆破壞掉 Done
Không chần chừ phá vỡ Done
(Go way up, way up)
Full shot pull it up Armageddon
Armageddon
(Aw wayo wayo wayo Warning all night long)
(Aw wayo wayo Warning all night long)
Armageddon
(Aw wayo wayo)
For both the end and the beginning
Akhir dan awal dari
終わりと始まりの
끝과 시작의
จุดจบและจุดเริ่มต้น
结束和开始的
結束與開始的
Sự bắt đầu và kết thúc
Armageddon